https://www.ukimediaevents.com/policies.php#privacy

Terms and Conditions of Business and Website Use
This website ukimediaevents.com ("the Site") is owned and operated by UKIP Media & Events Limited ("us", "our" or "we").
UKIP Media & Events Limited is a limited liability company incorporated in England and Wales with company registration No.05893940 and whose Registered Office is at 10 Queen Street Place, London, EC4R 1AG, United Kingdom and whose principal place of business is at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF.
Our trading name is UKi Media & Events.
Our VAT number is GB879 4451 71
We are registered members of the Association of Exhibition Organisers.
This document is only available in English and German.
The following constitutes a legal agreement between a visitor ("you") and us with respect to our website service, the terms of which are set out below. You must be at least 18 years of age to agree to and enter into this Agreement.
By continuing to use our Site, registering for an Event or purchasing a Conference Delegate Pass (“Pass”) for an Event you represent that (i) you have read, understood and agree to be bound by this Agreement and (ii) you are at least 18 years old.
If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of these terms and conditions, do not attempt to access the Site and do not register for an Event and do not purchase a Pass.
Our Site is established to give you information about UKi Media & Events, to assist you in choosing Events and publications that may be of interest to you and enable you to purchase Passes that we offer for sale online and to access our publications.
ACCESSING OUR SITE
Access to our Site is permitted on a temporary basis, and we reserve the right to withdraw or amend the service we provide on our Site without notice (see below). We will not be liable if for any reason our Site is unavailable at any time or for any period.
From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of our Site, or to our entire Site, to users who have registered with us.
You are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access our Site through your internet connection are aware of these Terms of Business and Website Use, and that they comply with them.
TERMS & CONDITIONS FOR PURCHASE OF A CONFERENCE DELEGATE PASS
Our website service permits you to purchase Passes from this Site. These purchases can be made and are permitted strictly pursuant to the terms and conditions set out below.
Your purchase cannot be accepted until payment in full for the Passes ordered has been received by us at which time a legally binding agreement on the terms set out in this Agreement will become effective.
PRICE & PAYMENT
Pricing and Delivery
Prices for Passes are stated on the secure payment form that you complete on the Site.
Methods of Payment
You can make a secure payment by credit card using our Secure Server.
You can pay using the following credit cards:
VISA
VISA Credit
VISA Electron
VISA Debit/Delta
Mastercard
Solo
American Express
Security
All of the credit card information sent to UKi Media & Events travels through a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) 'pipeline'. The information goes from your computer to our secure server. SSL is the most advanced security measure available.
The price that you have paid for Passes purchased by Credit or Debit Card will be shown on the Confirmation that you will receive by email after you have made payment.
When you purchase a Pass by Credit or Debit Card or if you have paid by invoice prior to the Event taking place, you will receive a bar code via email with your purchase confirmation. Upon arrival at the Event, this bar code should be scanned either from your smart phone or you can print it prior to your arrival and bring it with you to scan at the venue. Note in some cases we will mail you your Conference Delegate Badge prior to the event.
All credit/debit cardholders are subject to validation checks and authorisation by the card issuer. If the issuer of your payment card refuses or for any reason does not authorise payment to us, whether in advance of, or subsequent to, a payment, we will not be liable for any delay or non-delivery of the Passes ordered.
Booking Discounts
Discount codes must be used at the time of purchasing the Passes.
Group booking discounts can only be accepted upon purchases of Passes from the same company.
Substitutions
We will accept the substitution of one attendee for another upon written notification and with identification to prove the substitution is with the agreement of the original purchaser.
Order Errors and Cancellations
Passes for Events are subject to availability.
We shall be entitled to withdraw from any order for Passes made by you if the Pass is inaccurately described on the Site or where obvious errors have been made.
Cancellation Policy for Conference Bookings
* This cancellation policy does not apply to Exhibition or Media Sales Orders
We must receive all cancellations for Conference Bookings in writing prior to the Conference. The following information states the timescale and refunds due for different cancellation periods.
Cancellations received:
More than 30 days prior to the event - full refund/no payment due.
More than 14 days and up to 30 days prior to the event - 50% refund and 50% payment due.
14 days or less prior to the event - no refund/full payment due.
If you have paid for your Passes by credit card or debit card we will only make a refund to the original account used by you to make your purchase.
Marketing
We may request permission to send you emails and/or marketing material about our Events or publications which we hope you will agree to receive but we will not send any to you without your express consent.
Liability
UKi Media & Events do not accept liability for any loss of, or damage to, the personal property of attendees at an Event.
We reserve the right to cancel, defer or modify the Event without prior notice.
Complaints
It is in our interest to resolve any complaints as soon as they occur.
We will personally deal with all complaints as soon as possible, acknowledging your complaint within 48 hours and keeping you informed of our progress throughout the complaints procedure.
If you have a complaint, please do not hesitate to contact us at info@ukimediaevents.com
Attendance at the venue for the Event
We may arrange for photographs or video to be taken at the Event and it is possible that you might be included in any such photograph or video that may then be used in our marketing materials in the future. By attending the Event, you consent to such photographs and video, and their use for marketing purposes. Attendees may not make audio or audio-visual recordings at any venue.
You may not make audio or audio-visual recordings at any venue.
Consumer Rights
The terms and conditions in this Clause 2 do not affect your statutory rights as a consumer.
OUR RIGHT TO VARY THESE TERMS & CONDITIONS
We have the right to revise and amend these Terms and Conditions from time to time, for example, to reflect changes in market conditions affecting our business, changes in technology, changes in payment methods, changes in relevant laws and regulatory requirements and changes in our system's capabilities.
These Terms were most recently updated on 28 November 2018.
You will be subject to the policies and Terms and Conditions in force at the time that you order Passes from us, unless any change to those policies or these Terms and Conditions is required to be made by law or governmental authority (in which case it will apply to orders previously placed by you), or if we notify you of the change to those policies or these Terms and Conditions before we send you the invoice (in which case we have the right to assume that you have accepted the change to the Terms and Conditions).
YOUR AGREEMENTS
YOU AGREE that:-
It is your responsibility to provide accurate personal information ("Personal Data") and to update your Personal Data as necessary to keep it accurate. You undertake that all the details you provide to us for the purpose of selling and delivering Passes to you are correct and that the credit card or debit card that you propose to use is your own or that of a third party who has given you full permission and authority to use it and that you or such third party have sufficient funds to meet the costs of Passes ordered. We will not store your credit card or debit card details anywhere on the Site;
It is your responsibility to ensure that your email address is current otherwise certain functions of the Site will not be available to you. We will only use your Personal Data in accordance with the terms of our
Privacy and Cookies Policy
It is your responsibility to maintain the confidentiality and security of your Personal Data especially your user name and password. You will not allow others to use your user name or password and you will notify us immediately of any unauthorised use of either of them. We shall not be responsible for any losses arising out of the unauthorised use of your user name or password and you agree to indemnify and hold us harmless, for any improper, unauthorised or illegal uses of the same;
Whilst we will utilise anti-virus protections, it is your obligation to ensure that any use you make of our Site is free of any virus, Trojan horse, worm or any other items of a destructive nature. You will not hold us responsible for any damages that result from you accessing the Site (including any software or systems you use to access the Site);
You will not attempt or permit or encourage others to attempt to copy or make use of any intellectual property appearing on our Site for any commercial use or in any manner which would constitute an infringement of our copyright.
Variation in computer, browser and operation will create differences in visual layout and usability of the Site.
We have given due care and attention to minimising these differences, but cannot be held responsible for specific operational differences.
SYSTEM REQUIREMENTS
The computer, internet access and system operated by you and your ability to use the same may affect your ability to purchase any Pass from our Site. You acknowledge and agree that any system requirements necessary to preview, and /or view and/or purchase any Passes from our Site are your responsibility.
MISUSE OF THE SITE
We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your access to the Site or parts of it if at our sole discretion we believe you are in breach of any provision of this Agreement. If your access has been suspended or terminated you will not be permitted to re-register or to re-access the Site without our prior consent.
You will only use the Site for the purposes referred to in this Agreement and not access the Site or use information gathered from it to send unsolicited emails.
INDEMNITY
You agree to indemnify and hold harmless us, our directors, employees and consultants from and against any and all claims, losses, demands, causes of action and judgments (including solicitors' or attorneys' fees and court costs) arising from or concerning any breach by you of this Agreement and/or these Terms of Business and Use for your use of the Site and you agree to reimburse us on demand for any losses, costs or expenses we incur as a result thereof.
ASSIGNMENT
You may not transfer or otherwise deal with your rights and/or obligations under these Terms of Business and Use.
We may sub-contract, transfer or otherwise deal with our rights and/or obligations under these Terms of Business and Use in whole or in part
GENERAL
We have the right to withdraw any Event or Conference from the Site for any reason without notice to you and you agree that we will not be responsible for any loss, damage or cost as a result of such unavailability.
Our liability for losses you suffer as a result of us breaking this agreement is strictly limited to the purchase price of the Passes you purchased.
We will not be liable for errors or omissions on the Site nor for loss or damage suffered by you as a result of any unavailability of the Site or by any use by you or reliance placed on the Site or its contents including any damage caused to your computer or otherwise howsoever, or any direct, indirect or consequential loss or loss of data.
We shall not be liable to you for the failure of any equipment, data processing system or transmission link and will not be liable to you as a result of any down-time which may occur upon the Site.
The Site is provided "as is" and you acknowledge that despite our reasonable endeavours the Site may contain bugs, errors and other problems (including, but not by way of limitation) infection by viruses (despite anti-virus protections that may be incorporated) or anything else that may cause contamination or destruction of any sort that may cause system failures. Notwithstanding, we will use all reasonable endeavours to correct any errors and omissions as quickly as practicable after being notified by email to info@ukimediaevents.com
We shall not be responsible to you for damages or otherwise in respect of any error made to any listing of or reference to Events or Conferences.
We reserve the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently the Site (or any part thereof) without notice to you and without any liability to you or to any third party.
Links to third party websites on the Site are provided solely for your convenience. If you use these links, you leave the Site. We have not reviewed all of these third party websites and do not control and are not responsible for these websites or their content or availability. We therefore do not endorse or make any representations about them, or any material found there, or any results that may be obtained from using them. If you decide to access any of the third party websites linked to the Site, you do so entirely at your own risk.
We welcome 'hot links' to the Site, but not 'deep linking' by which we mean that you may not include a link to our Site, or display the contents of our Site, surrounded or framed or otherwise surrounded by content not originating from us without our consent. Any unauthorized framing of or linking to the Site will be investigated, and appropriate legal action will be taken, including without limitation, civil, criminal, and injunctive redress and may result in the termination of this Agreement or other remedies as set out in this Agreement.
It is the responsibility of advertisers on this Site to ensure that any content submitted by them for inclusion on the Site complies with applicable laws and regulations and we shall not be responsible for or liable to any extent for any error or inaccuracy that may appear in such content.
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS
All intellectual property content on the Site including, without limitation trademarks, button icons, logos, graphics and images is owned by us or licensed to us and is protected by International Copyright laws. Your use of them is governed by this Agreement, certain end-user licence agreements, and applicable law.
You will infringe our rights if you copy or reproduce any part of the Site save for:
a temporary copy of any part of the Site that is automatically made or retained by your browser as you browse the Site; or
you printing out any pages from the Site as a record of any Passes you have purchased from it; or
you printing out a copy of these Terms and Conditions which we would request you to do; or
your own personal use provided that:
no documents or related graphics on the Site are modified in any way;
no graphics on the Site are used separately from the corresponding text; and
the Company's copyright and trade mark notices and this permission notice appear in all copies.
Other than for the above four exceptions you must not copy the intellectual property in question for any purpose.
You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text.
Our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of content on our Site must always be acknowledged.
You must not use any part of the content on our Site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors.
If you print off, copy or download any part of our Site in breach of these terms of use, your right to use our Site will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made.
For the purposes of this Clause 10 "copy" and "copying" shall include non-literal copying as well as the copying of the structure and form of the Site and any elements within it.
DISCLAIMERS
To the extent that in a particular circumstance any disclaimer or limitation on damages or liability set out in this Agreement is prohibited by any law that is applicable, then, instead of the provisions hereof in such particular circumstance, we shall be entitled to the maximum disclaimers and/or limitations on damages and liability available at law or in equity by such applicable law and in no event shall such damages or liability exceed ten pounds (£10).
You understand and agree that your use of the Site is at your own sole risk. The Site is provided "as is" and without warranty by us, and, to the maximum extent allowed by applicable law, we expressly disclaim all warranties, express or implied including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose, and any warranty of non-infringement. We do not warrant, guarantee, or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the Site with respect to performance, accuracy, reliability, security capability or otherwise. You will not hold us responsible for any damages that result from you accessing (including any software or systems you use to access) the website service or using the Site including, but not limited to, infection by virus, damage to any computer, software or systems or portable devices you use to access the same. No oral or written information or advice given by any person shall create a warranty or a representation from us.
We make no warranty that any particular device or software you use will be compatible with this Site. It is your sole responsibility to ensure that your system(s) will function correctly with this Site.
Under no circumstances shall we be liable for any unauthorised use of the Site or Passes purchased from it.
Under no circumstances shall we be liable to you for any direct, indirect, consequential, incidental or special damages arising out of your use of or inability to use the Site, even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damages.
THIRD PARTY RIGHTS
This Agreement is only for the benefit of you and us and no other person can claim a benefit from this Agreement by virtue of the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999 that Act shall not apply to this Agreement.
LAW & LEGAL NOTICES
English Law governs this Agreement and your use of the Site, and you expressly agree that the English courts shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim or dispute between us or relating in any way to your use of this Site.
This Agreement and any other terms or documents referred to herein represent your entire agreement with us with respect to your use of this Site and the purchase of Passes via this Site.
If any part of this Agreement is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with the applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.
ACKNOWLEDGEMENTS
You acknowledge that we may change the terms of this Agreement by posting a new Agreement on the Site. You acknowledge that it is your responsibility to check the Site regularly to ascertain if changes have been made and your continued use of the Site after such a change will constitute your acceptance of the changes. By reading this Agreement together with our Privacy and Cookies Policy and continuing to use this Site you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions of this Agreement and by our
Privacy and Cookies Policy; Policy both of which are available from every page of our website ukimediaevents.com.
DISPUTE RESOLUTION
Please note that if you have a dispute with us that cannot be resolved amicably, the European Commission provides a platform (the “ODR platform”) for the out-of-court resolution of disputes concerning contractual obligations arising from online contracts for sales or services. The ODR platform is accessible via the following link: http://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr
Our email address is info@ukimediaevents.com
Site FAQs
Is it secure to give my credit card details over the internet?
Our site uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to provide encryption of personal information such as your name, address and credit card details. In this way, information passed between your computer and us cannot be read in the unlikely event of someone intercepting it.
What methods of payment do you accept?
We take the following major credit and debit cards: VISA, VISA Credit, VISA Electron, VISA Debit/Delta, Mastercard, Solo, American Express. Unfortunately, we cannot accept cheques, cash or postal orders on this web site. If you wish to use one of these payment methods, please contact us using the details below:
UKi Media & Events.
Abinger House
Church Street
Dorking
Surrey
RH4 1DF
Telephone: +44 (0) 1306 743744
Fax: +44 (0) 1306 742525
Email: info@ukimediaevents.com
What if I cannot find the answer to my question here?
Answers to the most common questions should appear here. If your question does not appear here, please email us at: info@ukimediaevents.com
What information will UKi Media & Events hold about me and is it safe?
We only hold the information you give us when you register. To see more information about personal information and security, please view our Terms and Conditions.
Privacy and Cookies Policy
We, UKIP Media & Events Ltd (incorporated and registered in England and Wales with company registration No.05893940) and whose registered office is at 10 Queen Street Place, London, EC4R 1AG, United Kingdom is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy & Cookies Policy (the “Policy”) sets out how we will treat your personal information and will inform you as to how we deal with personal information we obtain from you and how you may remove it.
We are registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office under Registration Number Z9745545.
This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”), together with our Terms of Use, Cookies Policy and any other document(s) referred to in them, sets out how we will treat your personal information, and is intended to help you understand how we deal with any personal information we may obtain from you and how you may access, alter, rectify and/or remove it. Under data protection legislation we are the Data Controller and we are required to notify you of the information contained in this Policy. It is important that you read this Policy so that you are aware of how and why we are using such information.
This Policy only relates to the collection, protection, disclosure and use of personal data belonging to individuals who visit www.ukimediaevents.com
(“our Site”) or who otherwise provide us with their personal information. It does not relate to data which emanates from companies or other entities, although the general principles regarding our collection and use of data is broadly the same irrespective of whoever is the user of our website, or our customer.
We will use your information only for the purposes for which it was collected.
This Policy has been prepared to meet the requirements of all relevant laws and regulations relating to data protection, whether local, national or supranational, including (i) the Data Protection Act 2018 (ii) the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 (iii) all applicable requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (the “GDPR”) and any national implementing laws, regulations and secondary legislation, as amended or updated from time to time, in the UK unless and until the GDPR is no longer directly applicable in the UK and then (iii) any successor legislation to the GDPR or the Data Protection Act 2018 and also The Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011, (the “Acts”).
By clicking the “Got It” button on the drop-down banner that will appear on the first page you enter on our Site you signify your acceptance of our Cookies Policy set out at Clauses 3 to 5 in this document. Please note that this banner will only appear the first time you enter the Site.
By providing your personal information to us, you agree that we may collect and use all personal information you provide to us in the ways described in this Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, please do not provide personal details to us.
Please note that we may need to update this Policy from time to time to reflect changes in the law. Any changes we may make to our Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. We recommend that you check this page regularly to ensure that you have read the most recent version and are happy with any changes.
This Policy was last revised on 18 October 2018.
INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU
It is your choice whether or not to provide us with personal information. Personal information (or ‘personal data’) means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).
The information we may collect from you includes, but is not limited to:
personal contact details such as name, title, address, telephone number, mobile number, email address, job title, fax number, your preferences for receiving marketing from us and your communication preferences that you may provide to us by filling in forms on our Site or at any of our events, or if you request information from us or when telephoning us;
correspondence, or a record of it if you should contact us;
details of your visits to our Site (including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own purposes or otherwise) and the resources that you access;
surveys that we use for research purposes, which we may ask you to complete, although you do not have to respond to them.
It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please advise us if your personal information changes during your relationship with us.
We may provide you with the option to select whether you would like to receive information from us by opting in or out of receiving promotional offers. In some circumstances, you will not have the option to opt out, for example, when we are administering a transaction requested by you, or if we are satisfying a legal requirement.
HOW DO WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION?
Ways in which you may be providing us with personal information include, for example,
registering on our Site;
contacting us with an enquiry;
signing up to receive a magazine, or to attend one of our events;
contacting us for more information about our events or magazines;
requesting us to forward your contact details to one of our advertisers;
reporting a problem.; and/or
giving us some feedback.
The information we may collect from you includes, but is not limited to, data concerning traffic on our Site, location data, weblogs and other communication data, (whether this is required for our billing purposes or otherwise) and the resources that you access.
By providing any personal information to us, you fully understand and clearly consent to the transfer, collection and processing of such personal information in accordance with the terms of this Policy.
IP ADDRESSES & COOKIES
Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone when you browse websites.
Our cookies help us:
Make our website work as you'd expect
Improve the speed/security of the site
Continuously improve our website for you
We do not use cookies to:
Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)
Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)
Pass personally identifiable data to third parties
Pay sales commissions
You can learn more about the cookies we use below.
MORE ABOUT OUR COOKIES
Anonymous Visitor Statistics Cookies
We use cookies to compile visitor statistics such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using (e.g. Mac or Windows which helps to identify when our site isn't working as it should for particular technologies), how long they spend on the site, what page they look at etc. This helps us to continuously improve our website. These so called "analytics" programs also tell us of, on an anonymous basis, how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before helping us to put more money into developing our services for you instead of marketing spend.
The cookies we use on this site are:
Name:
cookieconsent_status
Provider:
ANY OF OUR WEBSITES
Expires:
1 year from set/update
Description: This cookie is used to distinguish whether the cookie usage warning has been dismissed.
Name:
cookiesaccepted
Provider:
ANY OF OUR WEBSITES
Expires:
1 month from set/update
Description: This cookie is used to distinguish whether the cookie usage warning has been dismissed.
Name:
acceptCount
Provider:
ANY OF OUR WEBSITES
Expires:
1 year from set/update
Description: This cookie is used to distinguish whether the cookie usage warning has been dismissed.
Name:
PHPSESSID
Provider:
ANY OF OUR WEBSITES
Expires:
End of browser session
Description: This cookie is used to store your unique session ID on the website. It does not contain any personal information and is deleted as soon as you close all browser windows.
Name:
_newsletter
Provider:
ANY OF OUR WEBSITES
Expires:
1 year from set/update
Description: This cookie is used to determine if a visitor has signed up for a UKi Media and Events publication newsletter so that they are not repeatedly prompted.
Name:
ukip_publication
Provider:
ukimediaevents.com
Expires:
3 years from set/update
Description: This cookie is used to determine if a visitor has registered for a UKi Media and Events exhibition, conference or publication so that they are not repeatedly prompted.
Name:
__utma
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
2 years from set/update
Description: Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the JavaScript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Name:
__utmb
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
30 mins from set/update
Description: Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the JavaScript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Name:
__utmc
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
End of browser session
Description: Not used in ga.js. Set for interoperability with urchin.js. Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the__utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit.
Name:
__utmt
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
10 minutes from set/update
Description: This cookie is set by Google Analytics and is used to throttle the request rate for the service - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites.
Name:
__utmz
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
6 months from set/update
Description: Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the JavaScript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
Name:
_ga
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
2 years from set/update
Description: This cookie is set by the Google Analytics gtag.js and analytics.js scripts and is used to identify unique users.
Name:
_gid
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
24 hours from set/update
Description: This cookie is set by the Google Analytics gtag.js and analytics.js scripts and is used to identify unique users.
Name:
_gat
Provider:
google-analytics.com
Expires:
1 minute from set/update
Description: This cookie is set by the Google Analytics gtag.js and analytics.js scripts and is used to throttle the request rate for the service - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites.
Name:
test_cookie
Provider:
doubleclick.net
Expires:
1 minute from set/update
Description: Used by Google DoubleClick to determine if the website visitor's browser supports cookies.
Name:
IDE
Provider:
doubleclick.net
Expires:
1 year & 3 weeks
Description: Used by Google DoubleClick to measure the conversion rate of Google Ad campaigns we are tracking on behalf of our clients.
We are not part of the Google Ads network and do not publish adverts outside of our control.
Name:
SESSID
Provider:
app.ingo.me
Expires:
End of browser session
Description: Used by Ingo to allow our exhibition and conference visitors to register via social media accounts.
Name:
SIDCC
Provider:
google.com
Expires:
3 months from set/update
Description: Used by Google services such as Analytics and Maps to protect a user’s data from unauthorized access.
Name:
vuid
Provider:
vimeo.com
Expires:
2 years from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by Vimeo, a video sharing website, that we use to embed some content and is used to store a unique user id.
For more information click here.
Name:
player
Provider:
vimeo.com
Expires:
1 year from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by Vimeo, a video sharing website, that we use to embed some content and is used to remember a user's player mode preferences.
For more information click here.
Name:
ARPT_STATS
Provider:
secure.stats.zmags.com
Expires:
End of browser session
Description: This cookie is created by the Zmags Viewer that we use to publish online magazines and it is used by their load balancer.
Name:
zmagsPrivacy
Provider:
secure.stats.zmags.com
Expires:
10 years from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by the Zmags Viewer that we use to publish online magazines.
Name:
zmagsMobileVisitorID
Provider:
secure.stats.zmags.com
Expires:
10 years from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by the Zmags Viewer that we use to publish online magazines.
It is used to log visitor statistics such as pageflips and visitor location when a publication is viewed on a mobile device, but does not store any personally identifiable information.
Name:
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
Provider:
youtube.com
Expires:
6 months from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by YouTube, a service we use to embed video content.
It is used to determine whether the user is shown the new or old interface and is based upon available bandwidth.
Name:
YSC
Provider:
youtube.com
Expires:
End of browser session
Description: This cookie is created by YouTube, a service we use to embed video content.
It is used to register a unique ID to keep statistics of what videos from YouTube the user has seen.
Name:
PREF
Provider:
youtube.com
Expires:
8 months from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by YouTube, a service we use to embed video content.
It is used to store user preferences and can be used to personalise ads.
Name:
GPS
Provider:
youtube.com
Expires:
1 day from set/update
Description: This cookie is created by YouTube, a service we use to embed video content.
It is used to register a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location.
If you wish to know how to delete or manage the cookies we have set, please refer to www.allaboutcookies.org
For more information about the way in which Google Analytics uses cookies set by them, please visit the following link:
https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage
By continuing to use our website without changing your settings, you consent to our use of cookies as referred to above.
HOW TO DISABLE/ENABLE COOKIES
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. You can find out how to do this by checking your browser’s ‘Help’ menu.
For example, in Internet Explorer, you can go to Tools and then Internet Options, where there is the option to change your settings to disable cookies. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our Site if cookies are disabled.
You also have the ability to delete cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your browser. To do this you should search for “cookies” in your “Help” function for information on where to find your cookie folder.
Unless you have adjusted your browser settings so that it will refuse cookies, our Site will issue cookies on visiting, browsing and logging in.
To prevent Google Analytics cookies being set, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-On which is compatible with all major browsers by clicking on this link - http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout and following the instructions.
USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION BY US
We will only use personal information collected from you for the purposes for which it was collected (or for related purposes), to provide specific services that you request and to provide additional services that may be of interest to you, or in the following circumstances:
Ease of Use – To ensure that content from our Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
Transactional Purposes – To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, to respond to your queries and requests, maintain your accounts and manage transactions, such as credit card payments for any products that you order from us, or for the fulfilment of such transactions.
Communication – For example, to call you to confirm your registration details or to discuss your involvement in our events or your subscription to our magazines, or to notify you about changes to information we place on our Site or to our services.
Marketing Communications– We may use your personal information to communicate with you about our products and services, give you information and regular updates on our magazines and events depending on which brands you have subscribed to/registered for. You can expect to receive emails from us once in a while, and also some hard copy mail to give you more information about any magazine or event you have registered interest for; and we may also use your personal information for our own internal marketing analysis, for example, to assess trends amongst our consumers or to measure the amount of traffic to our Site.
Compliance – To comply with a legal duty or regulatory obligation to which we are subject.
Legitimate Interests – Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests, and when your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
Legitimate Interest means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by any adverse impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).
Any information or statistics relating to our business that we disclose to others shall not identify you personally. We may, for example, perform statistical analyses of the behaviour of the users of our website in order to measure interest in the various areas of our Site.
This information, and any other general information about our users that we share with others, will not contain personal information about you.
We will not, under any circumstances, sell your personal information to anyone else.
CHANGE OF PURPOSE
We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose.
If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please contact us by sending an email to us at datachanges@ukimediaevents.com or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom.
If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.
Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.
OPTING OUT
You can ask us to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by logging into the Site and checking or unchecking relevant boxes to adjust your marketing preferences or by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by sending an email to us at datachanges@ukimediaevents.com or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
Our Site may include links to third-party websites, plug-ins and applications. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave our Site, we encourage you to read the privacy notice of every website you visit.
HOW AND WHERE DO WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
All personal information we collect from you is stored on secure servers.
The personal information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”).
It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.
If your personal information is shared, you can expect a similar degree of protection in respect of your personal information because we require third parties to respect the security of your data and to take appropriate measures to protect your personal information in line with this Policy.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk.
Once we have received your personal data, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?
We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary for the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, and for the uses set out in this Policy. Where have no legal, accounting, or reporting requirements, we will not hold your personal information for more than 5 years from your last submission of data to us.
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information from your submission of data to us, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. In some circumstances we may anonymise your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.
DISCLOSURE BY US OF YOUR INFORMATION
We may disclose your personal information:
to third parties to whom you have provided your consent in order that they will be able to prepare or send communications to you,
to assist us in connection with any of our administrative or business functions, (including, but not limited to warehousing and delivery, marketing and advertising and credit card and data processing) or in the provision of any of our services and/or products to you.
to the auditing organisation ABC, so that they can verify `aggregated statistics about circulation and usage of our products or review our policies, processes and procedures for compliance with relevant standards. ABC will never share your personal information with anyone.
in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer.
if UKIP Media & Events Ltd., or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of UKIP Media & Events Ltd., our customers, or others.
This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.
DATA SECURITY
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.
YOUR RIGHTS
How can I access the information that you hold about me?
Under the GDPR you have the right to access information we hold about you (commonly known as a "data subject access request") free of charge. If you would like a copy of this information, please email us at datachanges@ukimediaevents.com or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom.
What if I don’t want you to hold my information any more?
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes.
You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by marking your preferences on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at datachanges@ukimediaevents.com or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom.
Can I change the information you hold about me?
Where you have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you withdraw your consent.
To withdraw your consent, please contact us on datachanges@ukimediaevents.com or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom. Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.
Under certain circumstances you also have the right to:
Request access to the personal information that we hold about you.
This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us.
It is important that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal information changes.
Request erasure of your personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal information where you have validly exercised your right to object to processing (see the provision below).
Object to processing of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms.
In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes.
Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal information in the following scenarios:
(a)     if you want us to establish the data's accuracy;
(b)     where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it;
(c)     where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or
(d)     you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it.
Request the transfer of your personal information to you or to a third party.
If you want to contact us with regards to the information we hold about you as above, please do so by emailing us datachanges@ukimediaevents.com
or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom.
You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.
We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access the information (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is another appropriate security measure to ensure that personal information is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it.
TIME LIMIT TO RESPOND TO YOU
We try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or if you have made a number of separate requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.
COMPLAINTS
You have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues at Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, or by telephone at 0303 123 1113.
CONTACT
Questions, comments and requests regarding this Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to marketing@ukimediaevents.com or writing to us at Data Controller, UKIP Media & Events Ltd at Abinger House, Church Street, Dorking, Surrey, RH4 1DF, United Kingdom.
Copyright © 2020 UKi Media & Events, a division of UKIP Media & Events Ltd
Terms and Conditions of Business and Website Use |
Privacy Policy |
Virtual Online Conferences Policies |
Cookie Policy |
Notice and Takedown Policy |
Site FAQs |
Advertiser Guidelines | COVID-19 update
X
Aerospace Testing International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Aircraft Interiors International
Also includes Airline Catering International and Airline Entertainment International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Automotive Testing Technology International
Also includes Crash Test Technology International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Business Airport International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Business Jet Interiors International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Engine + Powertrain Technology International
Also available: Automotive Testing Technology International has become the leading and most respected magazine covering breaking stories in the fields of vehicle reliability, durability, safety, quality, NVH, and dynamics testing and evaluation.
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Industrial Vehicle Technology International
Also includes Advanced Lift-Truck Technology International and Advanced Lift-Truck Technology International Off-Highway Edition
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Passenger Terminal World
Also includes Railway Terminal World
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Parcel and Postal Technology International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Professional Motorsport World
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Stadia
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Tire Technology International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Traffic Technology International
Also includes Tolltrans
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Winter Sports Technology International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
X
Autonomous Vehicle Technology International
Download the Tablet App now, for Android or iPad:
